<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Never Out of Water]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Never Out of Water]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/never-out-of-water/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 02:20:53 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/never-out-of-water/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 02:20:52 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>ABOUT US</strong></p>,<p>Water is the single most important necessity of life. For some of us, access to clean drinking water is as easy as turning on your faucet. But for nearly <strong>800 MILLION people</strong>, clean water just isn’t available. In most cases, men, women, and children have one single source of water that is so polluted and contaminated it has become a poison. As a result, more than 4,000 people die EVERY DAY! 9/10 of deaths that are a result of unsafe and contaminated water are children under the age of 5. It’s difficult to fully comprehend that kind of devastation. But focusing on stats and merely discussing the issues won’t help, it’s time to actively participate.</p>,<p>The NOW Coin Initiative is designed and developed to be a nonprofit organization. What does that mean? We are a registered <a href="http://kepler.sos.ca.gov/">Nonprofit Organization</a> and we’ve created a Crypto Charity and coin that lets a community actively participate in helping provide clean water. To do that we've teamed up with <a href="http://charitywater.org/">CharityWater.org</a> so that we can create campaigns and raise funds for clean water projects. Also, the community can easily track exactly how we are doing by visiting our campaign page.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/never-out-of-water/about-us/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2a063809-2243-4562-9383-449a60b7a47f</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 02:20:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/e42d5eaf-96ff-445c-84d1-e677f42d6f41.png">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/never-out-of-water/790c2691-4cc1-400e-a3c2-84ea1c8432d5/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">790c2691-4cc1-400e-a3c2-84ea1c8432d5</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 21:54:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>