<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Never Out of Water]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Never Out of Water]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/never-out-of-water/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 04:47:35 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/never-out-of-water/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 04:47:34 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ABOUT US]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1><strong>ABOUT US</strong></h1>,<p>Water is the single most important necessity of life. For some of us, access to clean drinking water is as easy as turning on your faucet. But for nearly <strong>800 MILLION people</strong>, clean water just isn’t available. In most cases, men, women, and children have one single source of water that is so polluted and contaminated it has become a poison. As a result, more than 4,000 people die EVERY DAY! 9/10 of deaths that are a result of unsafe and contaminated water are children under the age of 5. It’s difficult to fully comprehend that kind of devastation. But focusing on stats and merely discussing the issues won’t help, it’s time to actively participate.</p>,<p>The NOW Coin Initiative is designed and developed to be a nonprofit cryptocurrency. What does that mean? We’ve created a Crypto Charity and coin that lets a community actively participate in helping provide clean water. To do that we've teamed up with <a href="http://charitywater.org/">WATER.org</a> so that we can create campaigns and raise funds for clean water projects. The community can easily track exactly how we are doing by visiting our campaign page.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/never-out-of-water/about-us/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2a063809-2243-4562-9383-449a60b7a47f</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 04:41:06 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Save Lives by Mining + Using NOW Coin]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h2><strong>Save Lives by Mining + Using NOW Coin</strong></h2>,<p>We’ve built a unique function into the coin network so that everyone who mines or even uses NOW Coin will be helping save lives around the world. Every transaction will donate 0.1% of that transaction to the NOW Coin Wallet, here’s an example: I’ve mined 1,000 NOW Coins and I request a manual payout from my pool. As a result of this transaction 1 coin will be donated to the NOW Coin Wallet and the remaining 999 is sent to my wallet.</p>,<h2><strong>The NOW Coin Wallet</strong></h2>,<p>All donations will go to the NOW Wallet and from there will go towards helping people gain access to clean water around the world. To prevent flooding our own market with donated coins we will set a recurring schedule to exchange to BTC and work with companies so they start accepting NOW Coin and become longtime holders. This will help to prevent large sums building up over extended periods of time and exchanging all at once. We will also offer the community the ability to purchase NOW Coin from the NOW Wallet. Pricing will be established from a market average and the amount of coins available will depend on total donations to the NOW Coin Wallet. More details regarding this feature are soon to come!</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/never-out-of-water/save-lives-by-mining-using-now-coin/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3ea53054-455e-4e99-86d9-17afebf7d24c</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 04:40:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>